let mediumsubtractionquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 99 - 17",
        AnswerA: "79",
        AnswerB: "80",
        AnswerC: "81",
        AnswerD: "82",
        correctAnswer: "82",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 93 - 27",
        AnswerA: "63",
        AnswerB: "64",
        AnswerC: "65",
        AnswerD: "66",
        correctAnswer: "66",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 94 - 13",
        AnswerA: "81",
        AnswerB: "82",
        AnswerC: "83",
        AnswerD: "84",
        correctAnswer: "81",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 98 - 23",
        AnswerA: "74",
        AnswerB: "75",
        AnswerC: "76",
        AnswerD: "77",
        correctAnswer: "75",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 87 - 16",
        AnswerA: "71",
        AnswerB: "72",
        AnswerC: "73",
        AnswerD: "74",
        correctAnswer: "71",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 85 - 12",
        AnswerA: "73",
        AnswerB: "74",
        AnswerC: "75",
        AnswerD: "76",
        correctAnswer: "73",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 95 - 13",
        AnswerA: "80",
        AnswerB: "81",
        AnswerC: "82",
        AnswerD: "83",
        correctAnswer: "82",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 96 - 18",
        AnswerA: "75",
        AnswerB: "76",
        AnswerC: "77",
        AnswerD: "78",
        correctAnswer: "78",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 69 - 16",
        AnswerA: "51",
        AnswerB: "52",
        AnswerC: "53",
        AnswerD: "54",
        correctAnswer: "53",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 75 - 17",
        AnswerA: "56",
        AnswerB: "57",
        AnswerC: "58",
        AnswerD: "59",
        correctAnswer: "58",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 77 - 16",
        AnswerA: "61",
        AnswerB: "62",
        AnswerC: "63",
        AnswerD: "64",
        correctAnswer: "61",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 73 - 19",
        AnswerA: "53",
        AnswerB: "54",
        AnswerC: "55",
        AnswerD: "56",
        correctAnswer: "54",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 96 - 29",
        AnswerA: "67",
        AnswerB: "68",
        AnswerC: "69",
        AnswerD: "70",
        correctAnswer: "67",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 88 - 17",
        AnswerA: "64",
        AnswerB: "65",
        AnswerC: "66",
        AnswerD: "67",
        correctAnswer: "65",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 81 - 19",
        AnswerA: "61",
        AnswerB: "62",
        AnswerC: "63",
        AnswerD: "64",
        correctAnswer: "62",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 71 - 7",
        AnswerA: "64",
        AnswerB: "65",
        AnswerC: "66",
        AnswerD: "67",
        correctAnswer: "64",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 91 - 38",
        AnswerA: "51",
        AnswerB: "52",
        AnswerC: "53",
        AnswerD: "54",
        correctAnswer: "53",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 77 - 22",
        AnswerA: "52",
        AnswerB: "53",
        AnswerC: "54",
        AnswerD: "55",
        correctAnswer: "55",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 79 - 23",
        AnswerA: "53",
        AnswerB: "54",
        AnswerC: "55",
        AnswerD: "56",
        correctAnswer: "56",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 94 - 26",
        AnswerA: "65",
        AnswerB: "66",
        AnswerC: "67",
        AnswerD: "68",
        correctAnswer: "68",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 93 - 14",
        AnswerA: "76",
        AnswerB: "77",
        AnswerC: "78",
        AnswerD: "79",
        correctAnswer: "79",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 69 - 11",
        AnswerA: "56",
        AnswerB: "57",
        AnswerC: "58",
        AnswerD: "59",
        correctAnswer: "58",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 65 - 13",
        AnswerA: "52",
        AnswerB: "53",
        AnswerC: "54",
        AnswerD: "55",
        correctAnswer: "52",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 71 - 9",
        AnswerA: "62",
        AnswerB: "63",
        AnswerC: "64",
        AnswerD: "65",
        correctAnswer: "63",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 66 - 12",
        AnswerA: "53",
        AnswerB: "54",
        AnswerC: "55",
        AnswerD: "56",
        correctAnswer: "54",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 89 - 22",
        AnswerA: "64",
        AnswerB: "65",
        AnswerC: "66",
        AnswerD: "67",
        correctAnswer: "67",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 93 - 37",
        AnswerA: "56",
        AnswerB: "57",
        AnswerC: "58",
        AnswerD: "59",
        correctAnswer: "56",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 98 - 34",
        AnswerA: "61",
        AnswerB: "62",
        AnswerC: "63",
        AnswerD: "64",
        correctAnswer: "64",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 76 - 19",
        AnswerA: "55",
        AnswerB: "56",
        AnswerC: "57",
        AnswerD: "58",
        correctAnswer: "57",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 91 - 27",
        AnswerA: "63",
        AnswerB: "64",
        AnswerC: "65",
        AnswerD: "66",
        correctAnswer: "64",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 83 - 16",
        AnswerA: "65",
        AnswerB: "66",
        AnswerC: "67",
        AnswerD: "68",
        correctAnswer: "67",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 99 - 37",
        AnswerA: "61",
        AnswerB: "62",
        AnswerC: "63",
        AnswerD: "64",
        correctAnswer: "62",
    },
]